[{"answer": "Well, I --", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "It's not like you haven't had a few awards -- two Emmys, two SAGs, a Grammy, now a Tony may be heading your way?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "-- I'll treasure that.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Oh, you do?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "No, no Oscar.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "Is there anything you haven't won?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "It can work like that.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "Does it actually work like that?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "It's scary.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "It's scary, though?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Yes, because there is a point later on in the play when my character, Vivian, is in incredible, incredible pain.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "I mean, were you a bit staggered, like many people, by the way the Republican race went in its rhetoric about women's issues?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "You know, there are certain issues on which we can never do enough.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "But has he done enough as president?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Well, I certainly would like to see a bit more grit in terms of gay issues, in terms of LGBT issues.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "If he gets reelected, where do you want to see a bit more grit?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "-- I don't know if he's going to do that.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "-- if he gets reelected?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "Two children?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "And now you're going to be marrying a woman?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "You know, when -- when news of Christine's and my relationship broke, there was this tremendous, you know, we were on the cover of two New York daily newspapers.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "Did you expect what was coming your way?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think that the thing is that gay people, that there are a lot of myths about gay people, that they are -- they're sick, or they're -- they prey on children, or they're harmful to children, or they're causing the destruction of the -- of traditional straight marriage.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "How do you wrestle with people who've got religious convictions about it?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "I am definitely as happy as I've ever been.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Are you as happy as you've ever been in your life?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "No, no boyfriend.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Maybe the boyfriend will move in?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I think that \"Sex and the City\" showed that it was OK to be single, even if you were in your 30s, even if you were in your 40s, even if you were going to be single for the rest of your life.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "What -- what would you like its legacy to be to American women, do you think?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "So, six months?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "So we can spend pretty much every minute together?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "There were a lot of articles being written about, you know, single moms' sort of economic hardship and -- and sort of how they were supporting their families and the idea that a lot of women were having to help their husbands make money for the family and everything.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "But why did you want to do this?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "It's pretty even, actually.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Who likes it -- is it watched more by men or women?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "And you know about this phenomenon, do you?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Is it -- is that basically what this is all about?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "We saw that they were taking it down --", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 365, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 364}, {"answer": "-- what person decided, you know what, those need to be smaller, so I'm just going to --", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Yes, who did that?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "Without any involvement.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "I know, right?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Yes, they're in my home.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "You did?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "I haven't decided exactly where they're going to go yet.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "Where have you put them?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Do you think true love is out there, Jennifer?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "At some point hopefully.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "Waiting to lure you in?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "You left me.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "OVE HEWITT: I mean I think it's a great place.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "What is -- what is Hollywood like?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Have you ever been lured into the Hollywood temptations that bring so many of your peer group crashing to the ground?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Do you have sympathy for those that do?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "It's hard.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "What about this whole obsession with size zero and skinniness?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "It's fun.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 509, "question": "Do you like doing stuff like that?", "qSentId": 508}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "What do you think that person is like?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "If there are men watching this interview thinking, she's single?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I definitely dream of kids.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "In one of the many dreams that you have -- we have already discussed this -- do you dream of a wonderful, white wedding and then having kids and everything else?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "Well, sure, I think that would be more like coming at you.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Can you see how that could also, in the right place, be misconstrued as a mating signal?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Actually, I was going to ask you, it's a sad day for entertainment today.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Yes, which is very exciting, right?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "I was, yeah, big time.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Are you a fan of the band?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "It is sad.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "But it's a sad day, isn't it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Were they?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I'll award your one now.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "Why can't I have both?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "You can do that.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "Can I do that?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "Well, usually when I play matches, yes, the match is in my hands.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Tell me why you would say something like that?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "You know, when you're younger and you see the playground there, you see other things, you see your friends, or peers, going different places, and it's like, you know, you want to try that or you want to do that.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "But when you look at the incredible achievements that you and Venus have had, do you miss anything of that childhood that you had to sacrifice?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "First of all, I definitely think it would be in -- go to a tie break, because we both have amazing serves.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Who would win?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "I'm really, really ruthless out on the court, but so is Venus.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 709, "question": "Who's more ruthless when it really comes to it?", "qSentId": 708}, {"answer": "If it was down to limbs, they could take my limbs.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "You realize you just sentenced your sister to having all her limbs cut off?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Well, when you're out there, you have to take the winners attitude, at least I do.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "-- and you're winning, what do you experience?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "Well, I think I mean -- I never really got to see him fight, but I loved Mohammed Ali.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "Who are the people, in any sphere of life, historically or now, that you really put on a platform?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "Not 40-love.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "Forty-love?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "-- in the middle of this.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Isn't that crazy?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "This is your private jet boudoir.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Isn't that amazing?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 811, "question": "You wanted to share that with the rest of us?", "qSentId": 810}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 825, "question": "How?", "qSentId": 824}, {"answer": "You know, I think it has a little bit to do with my career, and you know, just making some decisions that aren't the right -- yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "How can you be single?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Well, I hope not.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 831, "question": "ORGAN: Do you know how many hearts broke all over the world when they read that?", "qSentId": 830}, {"answer": "No, I'm not going to withdraw that Tweet.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 833, "question": "Can you now withdraw that Tweet?", "qSentId": 832}, {"answer": "You know, I'm not ready yet.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 835, "question": "You're not going to never go out with another man again, are you?", "qSentId": 834}, {"answer": "It's not a fun space, actually.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "Doesn't it?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 850, "question": "Are you a romantic by nature?", "qSentId": 849}, {"answer": "Probably just once.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "How many times would you say you have been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 862, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 861}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 871, "question": "It's bad, isn't it?", "qSentId": 870}, {"answer": "I'm just curious.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "I don't want you to put that on me?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "They're -- our mission -- Missions is one of the companies that I'm owner of.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 893, "question": "For the viewers' point of view, what are they called?", "qSentId": 892}, {"answer": "You said some fighting words earlier on Twitter.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 914, "question": "Do I?", "qSentId": 913}, {"answer": "You will.", "docId": "120504pmt", "aSentId": 979, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 978}]